James A. Baker III Papers, 1957-2011 (bulk 1972-1992): Finding Aid MC197
Public Policy Papers
- Series 10: Presidential Campaigns, 1968-2000; 26 boxes
  - Subseries 10C. President Ford Committee (General Election), 1976-1978; 6 boxes
    - Research (miscellaneous), 1976; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - Scheduling, 1976; 1 box
      - Ford, Gerald, 1976; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 2)
      - Kissinger, Henry, 1976; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 3)
      - Reagan, Ronald, 1976; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous, 1976; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 5)
    - Telephone Call Slips, 1976; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous, 1976; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 7)
    - Post Election, 1976-1978; 1 box
      - Baker Draft of Statement on Election Loss, 1977; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence (Congratulations on Campaign), 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 9)
        includes letter from Dick Cheney
      - President Ford Committee Financial Results (surplus), 1977-1978; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 10)
      - Tribute to Jerry Ford Dinner, 1977; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 10D. George Bush for President (Republican Primary), 1968-1980; 4 boxes
    The Bush Republican Primary subseries documents Baker's work as head of the upstart Bush campaign and consists of notebooks, reports, correspondence, legal and financial documents, scheduling materials, and several folders of Baker's notes and memos. The correspondence grouping contains correspondence between Bush and Baker, as well as a small amount of Bush's outgoing correspondence. Also included in the subseries are legal and other documents relating to the Townhouse investigation, a Watergate-related investigation into Nixon slush funds which were given to candidates for various offices, including George Bush during his Senate Campaign in 1970.
    - Campaign Notebooks and Binders, 1979-1980; 1 box
      - Campaign Background Book, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 1)
        includes photographs of Bush and Bush family), 1980 1980
      - "Mission Impossible - Phase 1" report, 1980; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 2)
      - Issues Papers, 1979; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 3)
      - Clippings, 1980; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1979-1980; 1 box
      - Baker, 1979-1980; 1 box
        - Baker to George Bush, 1980; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 5)
        - Bush to Baker, 1979-1980; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 6)
        - Congratulations (Post-Iowa Primary), 1980; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 7)
        - Personal, 1980; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 8)
        - Reader Files, 1979; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 9)
        - Miscellaneous, 1980; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 10)
      - Bush, George, 1980; 1 box
        - Incoming, 1980; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 11)
        - Outgoing, 1980; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 12)
        - Material Sent Over Bush Signature, 1980; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 13)
      - Bush Family, 1980; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 14)
    - Convention, 1980; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 15)
    - Datebook, 1980; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 16)
    - Debates and Forums, 1979-1980; 1 box
      - Candidate Forum - Washington Hebrew Congregation, 1979-1980; 1 folder (Box 129, Folder 1)
      - Debates, 1980; 1 folder (Box 129, Folder 2)
    - Delegate Counts and Projections, 1980; 1 folder (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - Financial and Legal, 1970-1980; 1 box
      - Budgets, 1978-1980; 2 folders (Box 129, Folder 4-5)
      - Campaign Expenditures and Finance, 1970-1980; 1 folder (Box 129, Folder 6)
      - Federal Election Commission, 1978-1980; 1 folder (Box 129, Folder 7)
      - Fundraising (Baker for Attorney General Campaign Debt), 1980; 1 folder (Box 129, Folder 8)
      - Qualifying Blitz (Federal Matching Grants), 1978; 1 folder (Box 129, Folder 9)
      - Miscellaneous Legal, 1978-1980; 1 folder (Box 129, Folder 10)
    - Florida, 1979; 1 folder (Box 129, Folder 11)
    - Gridiron Club Speech, 1979; 1 folder (Box 129, Folder 12)
    - Invitations, 1980; 1 folder (Box 129, Folder 13)
    - Memoranda and Notes, 1979-1980; 2 folders (Box 129, Folder 14-15)
    - Schedules, 1979-1980; 1 box
      - General (Convention and Primary Dates), 1979-1980; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 1)
      - Baker, James, 1980; 1 box
        - Calendar and Date Book, 1980; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 2)
        - Travel Schedule Files, 1980; 15 folders (Box 130, Folder 3-17)
        - Miscellaneous Office Appointments and Meetings, 1980; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 18)
      - Bush, George, 1980; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 19)
      - Miscellaneous Travel Itineraries, 1980; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 20)
    - Secret Service and Security, 1980; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 21)
    - Staff Meetings, 1979-1980; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 22)
    - Staffing and Personnel, 1979-1980; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 23)
    - State Organizations and Field Contacts, 1979-1980; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 24)
    - Television Events - "Ask George Bush", 1980; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 25)
    - Townhouse Investigation, 1968-1980; 2 boxes
      - Bush Campaign Expenditures - Lists and Statements, 1968-1970; 2 folders (Box 130, Folder 26-27)
      - Clippings, 1973-1980; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence and Press Releases, 1980; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 2)
      - National Archives Documents, 1969-1980; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 3)
      - Miscellaneous, undated; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 4)
    - Trilateral Commission, 1980; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous, 1979-1980; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 10E. Reagan-Bush Committee (General Election), 1980-1981 January; 5 boxes
    The 1980 Reagan-Bush General Election subseries documents Baker's involvement with the Reagan-Bush Committee during the 1980 general election. The subseries contains correspondence, including a small amount of personal correspondence from George Bush, as well as administrative materials such as organizational charts and budgets. Also included are a campaign marketing plan, legal and financial documents, and scheduling materials for Baker, Bush, Reagan, and Gerald Ford. During the campaign Baker was given oversight of debate scheduling and logistics and the most substantial group of material within the subseries, the Debates and Debates Scheduling grouping, documents this role. Included is briefing material, correspondence between Baker, other members of the Reagan campaign team, and the Carter campaign, as well as notes on format and logistics, press releases, and memos relating to the debates and debate scheduling and logistics.
    - Administrative, 1980; 1 box
      - Budget, 1980; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 7)
      - Organizational Charts, 1980; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 8)
      - Reagan-Bush Headquarters List, 1980; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 9)
    - Campaign Notebooks and Binders, 1980; 2 boxes
      - "Campaign '80" Marketing Plan, 1980; 3 folders (Box 131, Folder 10-12)
      - "The Carter Record" (prepared by the Republican National Committee), 1980; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - Convention, 1980; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1980-1981 January; 2 boxes
      - George Bush - Personal, 1980; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 3)
      - 1980 May-June, 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 4)
      - 1980 July, 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 5)
      - 1980 August, 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 6)
      - 1980 September, 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 7)
      - 1980 October, 2 folders (Box 132, Folder 8-9)
      - 1980 November, 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 10)
      - Record of Mail Received, 1980 September-1981 January; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - Debates and Debates Scheduling, 1980; 2 boxes
      - Briefing materials, 1980; 1 box
        - General, 1980; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 2)
        - Closing Statement Drafts, 1980; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, 1980; 1 box
        - Baker to Reagan, 1980; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 4)
        - Carter Campaign, 1980; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 5)
        - Correspondence from Public, 1980; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 6)
      - Invitations, 1980; 1 box
        - General, 1980; 3 folders (Box 133, Folder 7-9)
        - Joint Center for Political Studies, 1980; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 10)
        - Ladies Home Journal/Women's Economic Roundtable, 1980; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 11)
        - Real Money, 1980; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 12)
        - World Research, Inc, 1980; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 13)
      - Format and Logistics, 1980; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 14)
      - League of Women Voters, 1980; 1 folder (Box 134, Folder 1)
      - Memoranda, 1980; 1 box
        - Baker Handwritten Notes, 1980; 1 folder (Box 134, Folder 2)
        - Carruthers, Bill, 1980; 1 folder (Box 134, Folder 3)
        - Gergen, Dave, 1980; 1 folder (Box 134, Folder 4)
        - Martel, Myles, 1980; 1 folder (Box 134, Folder 5)
        - Strategy Team, 1980; 1 folder (Box 134, Folder 6)
      - Panelists, 1980; 1 folder (Box 134, Folder 7)
      - Press Coverage, 1980; 1 folder (Box 134, Folder 8)
      - Reagan Statements and Press Releases, 1980; 1 folder (Box 134, Folder 9)
      - Miscellaneous, 1980; 1 folder (Box 134, Folder 10)
    - Democrats for Reagan, 1980; 1 folder (Box 134, Folder 11)
    - Legal, 1980; 1 box
      - Federal Election Commission, 1980; 1 folder (Box 134, Folder 12)
      - Expense Reimbursement Forms, 1980; 1 folder (Box 134, Folder 13)
    - Mailing and Mailing Lists, 1980; 1 folder (Box 134, Folder 14)
    - Memoranda, 1980; 1 folder (Box 134, Folder 15)
    - Nationalities Division, 1980; 1 folder (Box 134, Folder 16)
    - Press and Media, 1980; 1 box
      - Press Releases, 1980; 1 folder (Box 134, Folder 17)
      - Report on Media Plan, 1980; 1 folder (Box 134, Folder 18)
    - Reagan-Carter Phone Call, 1980; 1 folder (Box 134, Folder 19)
    - Resumes and Recommendations for Employment, 1980; 1 folder (Box 134, Folder 20)
    - Schedules, 1980; 1 box
      - Baker, 1980; 1 folder (Box 135, Folder 1)
      - Bush, 1980; 1 folder (Box 135, Folder 2)
      - Ford, 1980; 1 folder (Box 135, Folder 3)
      - Reagan, 1980; 1 folder (Box 135, Folder 4)
    - Telephone Messages, 1980; 4 folders (Box 135, Folder 5-8)
    - Television Events, 1980; 1 box
      - Election Eve Television Address, 1980; 1 folder (Box 135, Folder 9)
      - "Reagan Report" and "Ask George Bush", 1980; 1 folder (Box 135, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 10F. Reagan-Bush (General Election), 1982-1985; 2 boxes
    The 1984 General Election subseries is composed of materials related to the 1984 Presidential campaign of Ronald Reagan, a campaign that was essentially run from the White House Chief of Staff office. The subseries includes meeting agendas, debate briefing materials, debate planning information, and a variety of documents regarding general campaign strategy, as well as a bound Action Plan for the campaign.
    - Action Plan, 1983; 1 folder (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - Agendas for Weekly Political Meeting, 1984; 1 folder (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - American Coalition for Traditional Values, 1982-1985; 1 folder (Box 136, Folder 3)
    - Debates, 1984; 2 boxes
      - Briefing Materials, 1984; 2 folders (Box 136, Folder 4-5)
      - Memoranda, Press, Transcripts, Correspondence, 1984; 1 folder (Box 137, Folder 1)
      - Negotiations, 1984; 1 folder (Box 137, Folder 2)
      - Publicity, 1984; 1 folder (Box 137, Folder 3)
      - Scheduling and Sites, 1984; 1 folder (Box 137, Folder 4)
      - Site Planning, 1984; 1 folder (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - Reports and Memoranda, Miscellaneous, 1984; 1 folder (Box 137, Folder 6)
    - Platform Material, 1984; 1 folder (Box 137, Folder 7)
    - "Strategic Questions", 1984; 1 folder (Box 137, Folder 8)
    - Strategy and Fundraising, 1983; 1 folder (Box 137, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 10G. Bush-Quayle (General Election), 1988; 4 boxes
    The 1988 General Election subseries documents Baker's post-primary leadership of the 1988 Bush-Quayle campaign. It includes a variety of correspondence, including letters from such political figures as Margaret Thatcher, Ronald Reagan, and Richard Nixon, whose correspondence includes detailed analysis and strategy suggestions. The subseries also includes material related to presidential debates, including preparatory material and scheduling information, as well as Baker's notes from strategy sessions, and materials regarding a range of legal concerns such as Republican National Committee activities and campaign finance.
    Also included are files documenting communication between the Office of the Vice President in Washington and Bush's campaign operations. The files contain items, including memos and correspondence, sent between the two offices during the spring, summer and fall of 1988. (A small amount of material predates Baker's official involvement with the campaign, which began in August.) A substantial amount of the material in the files consists of carbon copied documents, often from Bush's outgoing and incoming correspondence, that Bush, Baker, or their staffs forwarded or copied to each other. The files also contain some notes and letters sent between Bush and Baker. Although most of the material is focused on the campaign, a few light-hearted notes are also present.
    - Clippings, 1988 August-November; 4 folders (Box 138, Folder 1-4)
    - Correspondence, 1988; 2 boxes
      - Alphabetical Files, 1988; 1 folder (Box 138, Folder 5)
      - Special Letters, 1988; 1 folder (Box 138, Folder 6)
        Includes correspondence from Margaret Thatcher, Ronald Reagan, and Richard Nixon
      - Miscellaneous, 1988; 1 folder (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - Daily Staff Meeting Agendas, 1988; 1 folder (Box 139, Folder 2)
    - Debates, 1988; 2 boxes
      - Memorandum of Understanding, 1988; 1 folder (Box 139, Folder 3)
      - Negotiations, 1988; 1 folder (Box 139, Folder 4)
      - Preparation Notebook, 1988; 2 folders (Box 139, Folder 5-6)
      - Preparations, 1988; 2 folders (Box 140, Folder 1-2)
      - Miscellaneous, 1988; 2 folders (Box 140, Folder 3-4)
    - Leadership on the Issues, 1988; 1 folder (Box 140, Folder 5)
    - Legal (Ede Holiday and Jan Baran), 1988; 1 folder (Box 140, Folder 6)
    - Notes and Assorted Papers, 1988; 2 folders (Box 140, Folder 7-8)
    - Office of the Vice President, 1988; 2 boxes
      - General, 1988 (1 Folder), 1 folder (Box 140, Folder 9)
      - General, 1988 (continued), 2 folders (Box 141, Folder 1-2)
      - Block Calendars, 1988; 1 folder (Box 141, Folder 3)
    - Strategy Session Notes, 1988; 1 folder (Box 141, Folder 4)
    - Remarks, 1988; 1 box
      - General, 1988; 1 folder (Box 141, Folder 5)
      - National Press Club, 1988; 1 folder (Box 141, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous, 1988; 1 box
      - 1988 April-July, 1 folder (Box 141, Folder 7)
      - Labeled "Hold for JAB", 1988; 1 folder (Box 141, Folder 8)
        Includes talking points for George Bush, memos and correspondence, and Baker's notes
  - Subseries 10H. Bush-Quayle (General Election), 1992; 1 box
    The 1992 General Election subseries contains debate preparation material for George Bush.
    The subseries is contains one folder of material.
    - Bush Debate Preparation Notebook, 1992; 1 folder (Box 141, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 10I. Dole-Kemp (General Election), 1996; 1 box
    The 1996 General Election subseries consists of debate preparation material for Bob Dole, as well as one small folder which includes loose documents related to debates and campaign strategy.
    - Dole Debate Briefing Book, 1996; 1 folder (Box 141, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous, 1996; 1 folder (Box 141, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 10J. Bush-Cheney (General Election), 2000; 2 boxes
    The 2000 election subseries documents Baker's role as chief spokesperson and head of George W. Bush's legal team during the 2000 Florida recount. The subseries consists of two binders of material as well as a scrapbook created by the Republican Party of Florida.
    Documents have been removed from binders for preservation purposes. The series includes copies of the Supreme Court of Florida and Supreme Court of the United States decisions related to the recount, including copies signed by all members of the Bush legal team, drafts of statements by Baker and Bush, and faxes and personal notes received by Baker when he was in Florida. Many of the faxes, statement drafts, and other material include Baker's handwritten notes and talking points.
    The Republican Party of Florida scrapbook consists of printouts of digital photographs of staff at the party headquarters during the recount effort. The book includes several photographs of Baker.
    The subseries arrangement reflects the original order of two binders, and one scrapbook of material.
    - Binder 1, 2000; 2 boxes
      - Table of Contents, 2000; 1 folder (Box 141, Folder 12)
      - Legal Documents, 2000; 1 folder (Box 141, Folder 13)
      - Supreme Court, 2000; 1 box
        - U. S. and Florida, 2000; 1 folder (Box 141, Folder 14)
        - Florida, 2000; 1 folder (Box 141, Folder 15)
      - Statements, 2000; 1 box
        - James A. Baker III Drafts, 2000; 2 folders (Box 142, Folder 1-2)
        - George W. Bush, 2000; 1 folder (Box 142, Folder 3)
      - Photograph, Baker et al., 2000; 1 folder (Box 142, Folder 4)
      - Press Briefings, 2000; 1 folder (Box 142, Folder 5)
    - Binder 2, 2000; 1 box
      - Table of Contents, 2000; 1 folder (Box 142, Folder 6)
      - Schedules, 2000; 1 folder (Box 142, Folder 7)
      - Television Interview Scripts, 2000; 1 folder (Box 142, Folder 8)
      - Received Faxes, 2000; 1 folder (Box 142, Folder 9)
      - Personal Notes, 2000; 1 folder (Box 142, Folder 10)
      - Miscellaneous, 2000; 1 folder (Box 142, Folder 11)
    - Republican Party of Florida Scrapbook, 2000; 1 folder (Box 142, Folder 12)
- Series 11: Speeches and Interviews, 1952-1995; 29 boxes
  The Speeches and Interviews series consists of speeches, lectures, interviews, remarks, and testimony given by Baker from 1975 to 1993 during his terms as Under Secretary of Commerce, Chief of Staff, Secretary of the Treasury, and Secretary of State. Speeches are arranged chronologically and divided into subseries corresponding to Baker's positions, with miscellaneous and undated material located at the end of each subseries. Folders generally contain the text of the speech as well as some background material.
  The series is arranged roughly chronologically in six subseries, with miscellaenoues and undated material located at the end of the series.
  - Subseries 11A. Under Secretary of Commerce, 1975-1976; 1 box
    The Undersecretary of Commerce subseries consists of speeches Baker made while serving as Undersecretary of Commerce in the Ford Administration from 1975 to 1976. Speeches are grouped by state in which the speech was given and chronologically within each grouping.
    Speeches are grouped by state in which the speech was given and chronologically within each grouping.
    - Alabama, 1975; 1 folder (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - California, 1976; 1 folder (Box 143, Folder 2)
    - Florida, 1976; 1 folder (Box 143, Folder 3)
    - Louisiana, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 143, Folder 4)
    - Massachusetts, 1976; 1 folder (Box 143, Folder 5)
    - Missouri, 1976; 1 folder (Box 143, Folder 6)
    - Pennsylvania, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 143, Folder 7)
    - New York, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 143, Folder 8)
    - Texas, 1976; 1 folder (Box 143, Folder 9)
    - Washington, D.C., 1975-1976; 1 box
      - House and Senate Statements, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 143, Folder 10)
      - Miscellaneous, 1976; 1 folder (Box 143, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 11B. Political and Miscellaneous, 1975 August 18-1979 December 1; 3 boxes
    The Political and Miscellaneous subseries consists of speeches made by Baker from 1976 to 1979 during a period in which he was active in both national and Texas state politics. The majority of the speeches were given in Texas in conjunction with Baker's run for attorney general. A smaller number of speeches address the 1976 presidential election and George Bush's planned presidential campaign in 1980.
    Speech files are arranged chronologically, with undated and miscellaneous speech material located at the end of the subseries.
    - New York Chamber of Commerce and Industry, 1976 May 17; 1 folder (Box 143, Folder 12)
    - Statement: "The High Cost of Regulation,", 1975 August 18; 1 folder (Box 143, Folder 13)
    - Northwest Academy (Houston, Texas), 1976 May 28; 1 folder (Box 143, Folder 14)
    - Gridiron Club (Washington, D.C.), 1976 December; 1 folder (Box 143, Folder 15)
    - Lincoln Day Dinner/Dance (Fort Bend County, Texas), 1977 February 19; 1 folder (Box 143, Folder 16)
    - River Oaks Breakfast Club (Houston, Texas?), 1977 February 24; 1 folder (Box 143, Folder 17)
    - Wiess College (Rice University), 1977 March 10; 1 folder (Box 143, Folder 18)
    - Houston Industrial Distributors Association, 1977 March 21; 1 folder (Box 143, Folder 19)
    - Harlan II Society (University of Texas), 1977 April 13; 1 folder (Box 143, Folder 20)
    - Richard Bradley Home (Houston, Texas), 1977 May 4; 1 folder (Box 143, Folder 21)
    - Propeller Club, 1977 May 18; 1 folder (Box 143, Folder 22)
    - Hill School Commencement (Pottstown, PA), 1977 May 22; 1 folder (Box 143, Folder 23)
    - Tejas Breakfast Club (Houston, Texas), 1977 June 16; 1 folder (Box 143, Folder 24)
    - Salute to Great Americans Dinner (Dallas, Texas), 1977 June 17; 1 folder (Box 144, Folder 1)
    - Republican Men's Club (Dallas, Texas), 1977 June 24; 1 folder (Box 144, Folder 2)
    - Houston Northwest Chamber of Commerce, 1977 June 28; 1 folder (Box 144, Folder 3)
    - Space Center Rotary Club (Houston, Texas), 1977 July 11; 1 folder (Box 144, Folder 4)
    - Greater Houston Young Adult Republican Club, 1977 July 07; 1 folder (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - Denver, CO Meeting, 1977 July 22; 1 folder (Box 144, Folder 6)
    - Republican County Chairmen (Austin, Texas), 1977 July 16; 1 folder (Box 144, Folder 7)
    - Rotary Club (San Antonio, Texas), 1977 September 7; 1 folder (Box 144, Folder 8)
    - Boston College – Presidential Campaign Politics, 1977 September 12; 1 folder (Box 144, Folder 9)
    - Salute to the Republic Dinner, 1977 October 20; 1 folder (Box 144, Folder 10)
    - Downtown Rotary Club – "George Bush Day,", 1977 October 27; 1 folder (Box 144, Folder 11)
    - State Republican Executive Committee (Austin, Texas), 1978 February 18; 1 folder (Box 144, Folder 12)
    - Lincoln Day Dinner (Galveston County, Texas), 1978 February 25; 1 folder (Box 144, Folder 13)
    - Ft. Worth Reception – Baker for Attorney General, 1978 March 10; 1 folder (Box 144, Folder 14)
    - Dallas Reception – Baker for Attorney General, 1978 March 28; 1 folder (Box 144, Folder 15)
    - Midland Reception – Baker for Attorney General, 1978 April 4; 1 folder (Box 144, Folder 16)
    - American Legion (Galveston, Texas), 1978 April 4; 1 folder (Box 144, Folder 17)
    - League of United Latin American Citizens (Austin, Texas), 1978 April 22; 1 folder (Box 144, Folder 18)
    - A Star Spangled Night of Tennis (Houston, Texas), 1978 May 2; 1 folder (Box 144, Folder 19)
    - New York Reception, 1978 May 17; 1 folder (Box 144, Folder 20)
    - Associated Builders and Contractors of Houston, 1978 June 7; 1 folder (Box 144, Folder 21)
    - Finger Party, 1978 June; 1 folder (Box 144, Folder 22)
    - Young Professional Breakfast (Houston, Texas), 1978 June 13; 1 folder (Box 144, Folder 23)
    - Bill Simon Function (Houston, Texas), 1978 June 20; 1 folder (Box 144, Folder 24)
    - Bill Simon Function (San Antonio, Texas), 1978 June 21; 1 folder (Box 144, Folder 25)
    - Sigma Delta Chi (Austin, Texas), 1978 June 28; 1 folder (Box 144, Folder 26)